How do I get there? Right.
我该怎么到达那里? 好.
Drive north on Route 93.
沿着93号公路往北开.
Take Route 1 north.
再上1号公路往北开.
Go over the Tobin Bridge.
开过托比(Tobin)桥
Keep on the 1 until you get to Saugus.
继续走1号公路 直到你到Saugus.
Take the exit by Walgreens.
从Walgreens的出口出去.
There are signs for Melrose and Stoneham. OK.
那儿有写着 Melrose and Stoneham. OK.
Go up the ramp,
上斜坡,
that's back over the bridge across Route 1.
返回桥上, 穿过1号公路.
Take the next right.
在下一个路口右转.
That's south on 1. back towards Boston.
沿1号公路往南. 朝波士顿往回开.
Then it's just down the highway about 300 feet on the right.
然后沿着高速公路走下去, 大约300英尺处 在右侧.
Ok great.
I'll see you there. Bye.
我会在那儿见你的. Bye.
93 North. Excellent. Uh oh.
93号公路往北. 棒极了. Uh oh.
Route 1 North. Over the Tobin Bridge.
1号公路往北. 过托比(Tobin)桥
Oh I love this song.
oh 我喜欢这首歌.
Entering Saugus... so far, so good.
正在进入Saugus...到目前为止, 一切顺利.
Take the exit for Melrose.
从Melrose这个出口出去.
Back across Route 1.
往回穿过1号公路.
South to Boston.
往南朝着波士顿.
Hi! I made it!
Hi! 我成功了!